[Cage of Shadows]
[Episode 2]
Master.
Why did you break in here without consent?
Didn't I tell you to wait for me
and take care of your mother?
I couldn't wait anymore.
My mother's condition suddenly worsened.
The doctor asked me
to fetch the antidote soon,
or she might not survive this month.
Only those on death row
would be brought to Lingya Tower.
How did you sneak in here?
The new top scholar was beheaded
and his body was discarded out of town.
The killer hasn't been caught yet.
I just turned myself in to the authorities
and took the fall.
Ridiculous!
You didn't commit any offense,
but everyone else in this tower
is a vicious criminal.
-Do you know how dangerous...
-I know.
You told me about it.
Once in Lingya Tower,
there are slim chances of survival.
I'll try to find the antidote
as soon as possible.
I'll also think of a way
to get you out of here.
But I'm already in here.
It's the eighth drum beat.
The incense is almost burned out.
You have to go now.
The exit is right in that alley.
Insert the key,
and the door will open.
Then you'll win this death match.
What are you waiting for?
Kill her now.
Do it!
Step back!
Don't come near me!
Watch out!
Why not continue?
I only brought one dart.
I'll have to pull it out
if I am to use it again.
Hold this.
Take it.
I, Dao, never use swords.
They're clunky and of no help,
just like men.
Thanks for your help.
I didn't come here to help you.
The only reason I'm here is that this girl
took the key to the exit door.
Yanzhi,
I was spotted by them when I just found
the key in the alley.
This is the key?
Yes.
It's the ninth drum beat.
How could you do that?
I thought you were on our side.
Don't you know the rules?
Only one of us
can get out of here alive.
It's true that only one can live,
but obviously it's not the person
who opens the door.
-Open up!
-Open the door!
Open the door now!
The bottom-level death match is over.
You've passed the challenge.
We've made it through.
This is great, Yanzhi.
Let's go.
I finally made a right bet!
Three survivors.
Isn't it against the rules?
Rules?
Since when are there so many rules
in Lingya Tower?
Now that all three girls
have made it through,
the result should be deemed as valid!
In that case,
how do we settle the bets?
Each of the two of you
bet right on one person.
So you can split the prize money equally.
Split it equally?
Of course you're happy now.
If these girls fight again,
the one named Jiang Man who you bet on
will definitely lose!
What do you want then?
Are we going to make them fight
another round?
Yes, absolutely!
For what reason?
I already made the right bet.
So did I!
Harmony brings wealth.
-Only one can be the winner.
-Harmony brings wealth.
I have a proposal.
Those girls
are all beautiful and gorgeous.
If the two distinguished guests of you
don't mind,
why not go have a good time with them?
Won't that be wonderful?
Then send that girl
with strong combat skills to me.
Wujiu.
Yes.
You heard what we said, didn't you?
Go make arrangements now.
Yes.
What's this place?
Yanzhi,
what does this mean?
What's this smell?
Here I come.
You shouldn't have targeted these girls.
[First Meeting]
There's a rabbit.
You...